# （*这里有一句话我听不清*）
[*Unintelligible*]
# 小三级头
Miniature Lv 3 Helmet
# 打算（？）今天把它做出来
I plan to finish it today
# 小刀
Little knife
# 小灶
Little Stove
# 别总说我做的东西没用
Stop saying my inventions are useless
# 做个蛋还是可以的
It cooks an egg
# 小枪
Miniature Gun
# 压水井
Water Pump
# 用过的都老了吧
You need to be of some age to have used this stuff
# 小火箭
Miniature Rocket
# 用变径和半圆头做的
I made it with a reducer and a cap
# 本想把它设计成不倒翁，但上面太重了
I initially wanted to make it like a roly-poly, but its top ends up too heavy
# 现在还比较粗糙，以后再打磨光亮
It looks a bit scruffy now. I will polish it shiny later
# 童年三件套
"Childhood Set"
# 童年三件套之
"Childhood Set" of
# 急速大风车
Super-speed Pinwheel
# 震耳拨浪鼓
Deafening Rattle-Drum
# 千里纸飞机
Paper Plane that could fly a thousand "Li" (i.e. 500 km)
# 千里不是钢飞机，千里铁飞机
Not a steel plane, an iron one
# 咻
Shoo--
# 这几天一直在做以前做的东西
I've been making some of my earlier inventions
# 像 （？）带呀，或者是，或者是
Like [*unintelligible*] belt, or,
# 手机壳儿
Phone cases
# 拍个视频，敷衍一下
Film a quick video
# 我怕你们忘了我
In case you guys have forgotten me